<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Home</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Home</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://luluslly.xyz/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Site/Life Update</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/12/08/site-update-dec08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/12/08/site-update-dec08/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Heya everyone. Long time, no see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I realize that I haven&amp;rsquo;t published a single blog post since September, which is something I do honestly feel really bad about. This site is meant to be an extension of my thoughts and feelings, painted onto a digital canvas of sorts. It kinda defeats the purpose of maintaining a web server and taking up precious bandwidth and hard drive storage space if you&amp;rsquo;re not doing anything with it, right? I think the least I could do is be transparent and let you guys know what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to in the mean time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Configuring a Corne-style Keyboard Layout Using Kanata</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/09/06/kanata-config/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/09/06/kanata-config/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As of late, I have been working on keeping up-to-date repositories of my various configuration files, which can now be viewed on my &lt;a href="https://git.luluslly.xyz/lulusilly/"&gt;Forgejo instance&lt;/a&gt;. One of the things I have put a decent amount of work into has been my daily-use keyboard layout. Seeing as I&amp;rsquo;ve fallen hook, line, and sinker for the ergonomic keyboard craze, I&amp;rsquo;ve come up with a relatively comfortable setup using the &lt;a href="https://github.com/jtroo/kanata"&gt;Kanata&lt;/a&gt; program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src="https://luluslly.xyz/images/kanata-icon.svg" alt="A white letter K imprinted on a pastel pink keyboard key cap Kanata logo"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kanata &amp;ndash; in simple terms &amp;ndash; is a &lt;strong&gt;keyboard remapper&lt;/strong&gt;. You can configure your keyboard to execute certain commands when a specific sequence of keys are pressed, do one-to-one remaps, and set up layers to allow you to access keys that would otherwise be a pain in the ass to enter traditionally.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>On Getting My First Split Mechanical Keyboard</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/08/02/on-getting-my-first-split-mech-keyboard/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/08/02/on-getting-my-first-split-mech-keyboard/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://luluslly.xyz/images/apple_setup.webp" alt="Image of a dark room with an Apple M4 MacBook Pro and 11th generation iPad A16with their screens on showing content and a split mechanical keyboard sitting between the MacBook's trackpad"&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;I finally got my first split, columnar, mechanical keyboard. It&amp;rsquo;s a relatively cheap one I found on Aliexpress, which you can find &lt;a href="https://www.aliexpress.com/item/1005008486363216.html"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="glazing-the-keyboard"&gt;Glazing the Keyboard&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since I got it, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working developing a sufficiently comfortable keyboard layout using only the 36 keys I&amp;rsquo;ve been allotted. Surprisingly, it&amp;rsquo;s not as bad as I originally figured it might be. Unlike my Alice-style keyboard I bought a while back, I have full &lt;a href="https://get.vial.today"&gt;Vial/QMK support&lt;/a&gt;. This is very beneficial to me since I absolutely require my &lt;a href="https://precondition.github.io/home-row-mods"&gt;home row mods&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://docs.qmk.fm/features/tap_dance"&gt;tap dance&lt;/a&gt; thumb keys to access all the necessary layers/modifier keys I use on a daily basis. It&amp;rsquo;s quite comfortable to use since I can slot it on the wrist rests on my laptops and still have room to use the trackpad for longer periods of mouse navigation (if only the mouse navigation layer were even &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; more comfortable!)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Initial Thoughts On My Newfound Apple Ecosystem</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/24/initial-thoughts-on-my-newfound-apple-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/24/initial-thoughts-on-my-newfound-apple-ecosystem/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll be straight to the point: Last Saturday, I purchased the M4 MacBook Pro. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t really had the full Mac experience before—I had only used a late 2000s unibody MacBook with a broken trackpad and a dead battery running High Sierra. I already own a decent amount of Windows machines (with the majority being laptops), but my most used devices were Apple products: my iPhone 12, my numerous iPads, and even my now-broken pair of AirPods Max.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Playing Around With Swipe Type</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/22/playing-around-with-swipe-type/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/22/playing-around-with-swipe-type/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday night I decided out of curiosity to try the swipe type feature found in most modern mobile operating systems. Swipe type, to be brief, allows you to take your finger and glide it across your phone&amp;rsquo;s on-screen keyboard without removing your finger from the screen; this allows you to form words and sentences without having to manually type out every single word by hand &amp;ndash; or I guess in this case, thumb.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>A Poem I Made</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/20/poem-i-made/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/20/poem-i-made/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I wrote the below poem on 2025-04-25. Not an instant classic, but simply an expression of my feelings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;code&gt;i yearn to be with another being
a lifelog bond where our memories and experiences intertwine
our sorrows, our joy, our anger
all together
a collective conscious
our deaths will leave behind our souls to dwell in the people we touched
the people we helped, the people we knew and loved
that will be our legacy
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description></item><item><title>The First Post!</title><link>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/18/the-first-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://luluslly.xyz/post/2025/07/18/the-first-post/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="the-first-post"&gt;The First Post!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#433e56;-moz-tab-size:2;-o-tab-size:2;tab-size:2;"&gt;&lt;code class="language-lisp" data-lang="lisp"&gt;&lt;span style="display:flex;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;(display &lt;span style="color:#1bc5e0"&gt;&amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;)
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>